comicspriceguide.com 2019-12-11

# 

## Privacy Policy

All the mumbo jumbo.

* * *

### Legal Notice

ComicsPriceGuide® is a registered trademark. All the materials at this site are protected by United States Copyright Laws, and any unauthorized reproduction, preparation of derivative works, distribution (whether by state or other transfer of ownership, or by rental, lease or lending), or other display of the copyrighted work publicly, without the express written consent of comicspriceguide.com is expressly prohibited, and any violation could expose the user to both criminal and civil liability.

### About CPG

CPG is an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through a network of comic book and collectibles fans. CPG members can view each others' profiles, communicate with others, post comments, and describe their sports interests. CPG members can change their profile information at any time.

If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at support@comicspriceguide.com.

### Privacy Policy and Statement

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users on CPG's network of sites, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.

This statement discloses the privacy practices for all of CPG Media's Web sites.

### Information We Collect

CPG collects information in several ways from our Web sites.

> #### Information Collection and Use by CPG
> 
> CPG collects user submitted information such as name and email address to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the CPG service. CPG also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, comic interests and zip code in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. CPG also collects user information when you enter a survey (internal research), sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by CPG and/or our partners. Wherever CPG collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.
> 
> Users within a personal network communicate on CPG with each other through the CPG service, without disclosing their email addresses. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, CPG allows users to search for other members using username and like interests.
> 
> We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by using the unsubscribe feature found at the bottom of any email or newsletter or through the Account Settings page.
> 
> Please note that a valid e-mail address is required for a CPG Web site membership. You will not receive your confirmation if your e-mail address is entered incorrectly.
> 
> CPG also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.
> 
> In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information.
> 
> CPG's sites also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.
> 
> If you choose to establish a credit account with us, we collect some additional information, including billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date.
> 
> If you choose to post messages in newsgroups or leave feedback for other users, we will collect such information about you as you choose to disclose.
> 
> #### **How Does CPG use your Information?**
> 
> CPG uses any information voluntarily given by you to enhance your experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of you and the rest of our users.
> 
> CPG utilizes information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out newsletters to subscribers. Third Party emails are also sent to subscribers.
> 
> CPG does internal research on our user's demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, or from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.
> 
> #### **Our Disclosure of Your Information.**
> 
> We do not share information about individual users with any third party, except in the case of some contests and sweepstakes—and then, only with a user's express consent. CPG does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly.
> 
> Throughout the site, you are identified by your User ID. Your User ID can be used to identify your activities throughout our sites.
> 
> CPG will disclose information, at its sole discretion, to law enforcement or other government agencies, or to financial institutions investigating fraudulent activities, as is deemed necessary and/or appropriate.

### Use of Cookies

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, CPG sites use "cookies" to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that tracks the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. All sites on CPG where you are prompted to login or that are customizable require that you accept cookies.

Advertising networks that serve ads onto any of CPG's sites may also use their own cookies.

From time to time, CPG and/or CPG advertisers may offer contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information includes name and email address; in some cases, the user must answer mandatory survey questions about a range of other personal data. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's identity, to send the entrant an email notification that their entry has been received, and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. There are two situations in which CPG will divulge this information to a third party--provided the user gives express consent:

  * A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to the advertiser.
  * Some of the contests may be hosted on the CPG site but administered by the sponsor; in such cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third party as long as that user gives express consent.

Because the rules and terms of each contest can vary, all information about each contest is clearly posted during the event. All contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws.

### **Links**

CPG contains links to sites. CPG is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on CPG.

### **Discussions and Articles**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information on CPG or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

### **Security**

CPG member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. CPG takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on CPG, please contact us a support@comicspriceguide.com.

### Third Party Collectors of Information

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on comicspriceguide.com or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Since CPG does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Deleting or Changing Your Registration Information

Upon request, CPG will remove credit card number and credit card expiration date from the membership file. Requests are to be forwarded to support@comicspriceguide.com.

You may review and change your email subscriptions and/or registration information, including your password, name, address, phone number, and email address, by editing your profile in Account Tools.

You may change your credit card number and credit card expiration date on file by accessing the Account Tools Basics tab.

Requests for removal of your registration information does not ensure that such information will be completely removed from the CPG system. CPG does retain registration information as a record of all activity performed on the site. Additionally, information is retained in order to enforce the Terms of Agreement, resolve disputes and problems associated with the site.

Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in newsgroups or other message areas.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on the CPG site for 30 days.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

ComicsPriceGuide.com  
212 W. 10th St  
Ste. A470  
Indianapolis, IN 46202  
support@comicspriceguide.com
